Sujitha Wijewantha

Software Engineer

ABOUT ME

Hi there, Im software engineer that enjoys creating amazing digital products. I've worked on multiple areas of tech from Mobile, Web and also Backend Developement. Currently Im focussed on building amazing experinces for Web3 based solutions.

EXPERIENCE

Enactor LTD

2021 - Current

- Migrating existing features in legacy POS to the Enactors ReactPOS
- Added new data preprocessors for the platform
- Contributed in helping streamlining the styling system used in the ReactPos
- Automation for existing features for the React POS

Affno Pvt Ltd

2019 - 2020

Completed a one year internship at Affno Pvt Ltd as a Web and Mobile developer

- Worked as a part of the web and solutions based team
- Performed development work with industry standards and best practices in mind
- Gained knowledge in the Web, Mobile and Server-side development by working on different frameworks such as Ionic, Laravel, Express
- Worked on multiple projects in areas such as Frontend Integration and Implementation (REST API, HTML, CSS)
- Created multiple chatbots for a better customer experience in websites

EDUCATION

Informatics institue of Technology

2018 - 2021

Bachelor of Science (BSc) Honours in Computer Science *First Honours*

Ananda College

2009 - 2016

Completed GCE O/L in 2015



Contact Me

% 0711833115 / 0714213832

O Colombo Rajigiriya

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/s ujitha-wijewantha-457bb915b/

Database

PostgreSQL, MySQL, Firestore

Design Tools

Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma

Programming Languages

Typescript, Javascript, Java, Dart, SASS, SQL

Frameworks

Flutter, Angular, NextJs, Express, React, Ionic with Angular, NestJS, Anchor

Languages

English Sinhala

PROJECTS

High Table Society

A writing platform experiment that aims on creating a story where it gets shaped by user input.

http://hightablesociety.com/

Tech Stack - Anchor, React, Tailwind

Carbon Planter

A product that aims at providing event organizers with a brand new, unique experience which aims on making events carbon neutral by gifting attendees trees.

https://app.carbonplanter.com/

Tech Stack - Tailwind, React, Typescript

PlayHQ

A mobile application that allows gamers to easily buy, sell, discover games with ease.

Tech Stack - Fluttter, NestJS, Postgres, GCP

Selective Pose Estimator

A prototype developed for the final year, that uses pose estimation and image processing to help ease the animation workflow of game developers and animators by allowing them to extract human movements from videos onto an animation which can be exported to a 3D software (Blender)

Tech Stack - OpenCV, Blender, Detectron, Python, Pytorch

FoodPal

A mobile-based application that recommends the user food recipes based on the ingredients that are available in the users' kitchen and based on the users eating preference.

Tech Stack - Firebase functions, Flutter

Referees

Suganthan Thiyagarajah
Tech Lead & Senior PHP
Developer at Affno (Pvt) LTD
suganthan@affno.lk
0773676575

Nadeesha Gamage
Associate Director/Solutions
Architect at WSO2
nadeesha@wso2.com
0773945706